[{"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JFG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "HGI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to bank H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "DFI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to house A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JEIC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to store B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "CH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to house I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "IJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "DG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "FDG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to school H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "EI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JIHC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to school A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "JGH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to house I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to cinema G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "ADFH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "JIHG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to house A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "JGI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "HIE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "BH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "EBDF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "GC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to store B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "ECGB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to cinema C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "DF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to store C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "HAI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to school A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "HGA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GBD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to school H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FGBJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to bank F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "G"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to store J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CFB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "JI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to school A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to cinema F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "DHG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to bank A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "HDEA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to bank H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "EDF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EGF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "BE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "ECJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to school H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IBAD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to cinema C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HEGB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "DAI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "IFE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "HEG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "GHACD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "HDFI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "AJH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "IB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to school I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EJG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to store C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EBDH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "HDCG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "IFGJC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to cinema D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "GD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to school D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "EJAG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "CJBGD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "DG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "AGHF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HJCD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to house G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "FB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to garden G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "BH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to store C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "AH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to cinema G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "CBHDE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GCIH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to garden H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HDA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to store D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FJGA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CDH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to house C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "IFHBJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HJD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to bank H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FGAED"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to bank G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "IBFA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to school D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "HEB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "FBJG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EJCADG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "JE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to garden A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "ICFB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to bank G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "ABJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to bank B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "DI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to cinema F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BFI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "JAD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "JEB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to cinema J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "AI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to school C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "HGA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "JG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GEB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BHI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to store C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EBFJH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "DJABE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "GDJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "FB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "ICH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "EJC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to house A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "JGDI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "HD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "DCEA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "D"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "CF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "GD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "JB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to school I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "JDAFG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to garden G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "CFHEJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to school D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to bank G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "FDI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to house I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "HAB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to school H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "JC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "JE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to school J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CDIG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "AEDI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "GFJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to house G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "DA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EFDGH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to school I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "DGC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to cinema J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "GBA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to garden G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "AE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to house C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to bank A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IJG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to bank H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "A"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to garden H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "JGI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to garden A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "EH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "FGED"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "JBH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to bank A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "FHBA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "DGHI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to bank B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "EAJDI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "FEJCB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to school H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "FE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to house A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "GH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "CBDH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to school J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "ECIBF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to cinema G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "DI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to house C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "EBF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "AED"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to cinema G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "EH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to school H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FAH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IHBA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to cinema C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FIDB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to garden A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "F"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to garden H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "BIF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to school J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "HEF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to bank B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "DG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "DEB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to school A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "JH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to cinema J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "IADGH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to cinema C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "DEI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "JE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to house G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "AEIDF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "BAF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to garden A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BGDIC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "IECF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DAC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to garden G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BDJC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to bank H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "AFD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EBCJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to store B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "JHA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JACFG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to cinema D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "IJGB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to school I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "GD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "CB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to garden J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "AHB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CIJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "DB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to cinema I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JHA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to house G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "FBAI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "GD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JBG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "IFCAGH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to store D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "AI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to cinema C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "AJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CAH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "FE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to cinema I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GHDJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to garden A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "CEFIJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "FG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "AIHGD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "EH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to house B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "AG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "JID"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to garden A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "JI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "FJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to store D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "FIA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to cinema C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "DC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "FB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to cinema D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BGH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "HEAJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to house B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DCB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to store B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JAFI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "DA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to school D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "ED"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "AF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "FDB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "GHBD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to cinema G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "HJG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "HCG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CDBE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to bank F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "JBI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CBH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "IJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "CJG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "IGBD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to cinema C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "DCAG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to bank F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "EDHJF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "DG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to house J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to cinema B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "FHCEJA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "GB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to house G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "EBD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "BGIJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to garden D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GBEIC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to cinema C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "ABC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to cinema C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HDI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "CFGJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to garden G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "EB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to school D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JBHD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to cinema J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to garden D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BFA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to bank B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "DH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to school H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "IAH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to house C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JBGA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "IEGB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to garden A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BHIEDA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to bank D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "HI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to store E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "IGD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "IH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "AJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to store J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "ED"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "CADG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to garden H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "JCI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "GE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to house G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "CD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GEI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "C"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JIA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "AB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "GJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to store C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "HA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to garden G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "AC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HAD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "ED"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to garden G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "DJI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "ICAG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to garden D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "BCFE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "AF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "DFICGA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "AHCI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to bank B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CADJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to store J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to school B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "HIB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "FJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to bank D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "EIFG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to cinema F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to house B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HGCA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BIAJC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to house J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HGC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BJD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to bank G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JEFB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to garden D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "IFB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "FGC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to cinema I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "ADE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "AE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to house J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "CFHJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to school B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "JE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "HD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to bank F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "DEB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FGABE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "AB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to bank A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to house B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "GD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "BH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to cinema C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "IAJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to bank A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "EIC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GHJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to cinema I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HBE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to store J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "GBHE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to house B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "ED"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GFBC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "CA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to school A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FIHA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to store D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "ACG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to house A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to garden J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "GAHD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "GBEH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "BH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to store B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GJA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to garden J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DFH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "IA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CHE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to store J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "EH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to garden G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "BFIE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to school I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "EB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "HIA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to school H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "CI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to bank G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "ACD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "ACI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "AHDGBI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to garden D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "AF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to house A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "BJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BGA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to house G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CBHAJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to cinema F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EBJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to store D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "EJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GEJI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to cinema J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "CHEI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BDJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "BFA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to store B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to house A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DCHA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to cinema B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "GIJHC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "IF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "EJIG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "J"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to cinema J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "EFGJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BACFIH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to bank G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "CB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "ECJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to store D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to school H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DGAFE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "JI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to garden D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GBEA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "FCHB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to house G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CHEBJA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GEH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to school A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "JHCE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "GJF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to house J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "B"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to house B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "HIE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "EG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BCJHI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "C"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to cinema D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "EFABGC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to garden G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "DF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to bank H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "GCD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to store B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "F"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to store D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BEI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "AIDBH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CBGD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "JB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "JE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to school J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "HD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CIGE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FDEB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "DCFBJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to store J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IBAE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to cinema G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "FHE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to bank A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "DA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to bank H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DCABG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to bank G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "ADH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "IG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to school C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to bank D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "IEJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GHD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to cinema F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "HEB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to bank A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "GCB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "EF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "IDEJC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "EA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "D"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to bank H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "FHA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "HBG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to school C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "FHAEJI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to house J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to school J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CHD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to garden D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "CHIBFGJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "ED"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "GIC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "IJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "BH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "JCHE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to cinema J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "BH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to store B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "DIJGEC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to store D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "CAIJF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "FHD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to school I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BGAEH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to house G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to cinema C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JDI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to house I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "HJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FBH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "AEBD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "EH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "AJH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to garden J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "GCI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "AI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FJB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to store C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "DJI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to bank H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IEDG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JAF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "I"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JDI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "BF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "IGHF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DIAH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "AGB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "IJH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to cinema C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to garden H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "ABFJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "FHD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "CB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to house I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HFI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "EHICB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to cinema F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "BA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "GFA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to school B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "IEADC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to cinema J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GHB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to house B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CIF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to bank G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FHJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "HIG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to cinema J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "IEAD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "C"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to bank F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to house J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "IH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BFE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DCAE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "HBA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FJB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CHA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "GAHC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "GCAH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to school I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "ACE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "HAG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to school B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "EJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to school D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "JEG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to bank D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "IG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to bank H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GJI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to bank H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "FBJDC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to cinema J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "EIAF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to cinema J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "EI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "JDAIE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to bank B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "IEF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "IJH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "HACG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to store E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "ABCJF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to garden G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DFB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "G"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "AICBHJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to school A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BDH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "EBC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to school I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "CEH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "GECFH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "BA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to cinema D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "HBAJE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to bank A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "DFC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "IF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to cinema I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "JBFI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to bank B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "FCE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to school I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JDEA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to garden H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BEAC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "CIB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to cinema C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "JEC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BFIH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "AGHF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to bank D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "BEIF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to school J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "ABG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "DF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to garden A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "ECG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "EB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to house I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "DFGJE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to house C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "GE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CJA"}]